mirrorupload.net 2016-02-05

# MirrorUpload.net - Privacy Policy

#### Logging IP Addresses.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or e-mail address. IP addresses are logged and used by MirrorUpload.net for measuring usage.

#### Collecting e-mail Addresses.

We automatically collect certain information about your computer when you visit our website, for example, e-mail addresses that you entrust us with affinity to record and measure the use of the website. MirrorUpload.net can not rent, sell, or share your personal information with unaffiliated companies.

#### Certain Exceptional Disclosures.

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or in connection with any legal process.

#### Use of Cookies.

MirrorUpload.net uses cookies to store the preferences and tracking trends of users. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. However, some MirrorUpload.net features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

#### How we protect your information.

We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.

We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required.

#### External Links.

If any part of the MirrorUpload.net website links you to other websites, those websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing personal information.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy.

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. MirrorUpload.net may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

#### How you can contact us.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us here](http://www.mirrorupload.net/contact.html). When we receive formal written complaints at this address, we will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints.
